{
    "subject": "resource/Dale_Brown",
    "predicate": "property/birthDate",
    "object": "1956-11-02",
    "human_readable": "Dale Brown was born on November 2, 1956.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8935650587081909,
            "question": "Is Dale Brown's birthdate November 2nd?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8164380788803101,
            "question": "How old was Dale Brown on November 2nd, 1957?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7788278460502625,
            "question": "When was Dale Brown born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6314714550971985,
            "question": "What is Dale Brown's birthdate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5989872217178345,
            "question": "What month was Dale Brown born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4382617175579071,
            "question": "Was Dale Brown born in the 20th century?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42849844694137573,
            "question": "What day of the week was Dale Brown born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33006367087364197,
            "question": "Is there a famous person named Dale Brown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30617213249206543,
            "question": "In what year did Dale Brown come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22011616826057434,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Dale Brown?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Dale Brown was born on November 2, 1956.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2575_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Dale Brown come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2575_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a famous person named Dale Brown?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2575_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What day of the week was Dale Brown born?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2575_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2575_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2575_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2575_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2575_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2575_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2575_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2575_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2575_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2575_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2575_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide consistent information that Dale Brown was indeed born on November 2, 1956."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}